Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- A, 1891-2012; 13.75 Linear Feet in 13 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Attica Defense Fund, undated (Box 13)
  - Attica Defense, circa 1970s (Box 13)
  - August 26 Strike Committee, 1970, undated (Box 13)
  - August 29th Movement, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    August 29th Movement was a communist organization.
  - Augustus M. Kelly (Firm) (New York, NY), 1967 (Box 13)
  - Australian Anarchist Centenary Celebration Collective, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Australian Labor Party, 1928-1958 (Box 13)
  - Australian Socialist League, undated (Box 13)
  - Australian Society for the Study of Labour History, 1962-1968 (Box 13)
  - Automation House, undated (Box 13)
  - Automobile Manufacturers Association, 1965, undated (Box 13)
  - Autonomedia, 1999- (Box 13)
  - Autonomista.org, undated (Box 13)
    Autonomista.org was an anti-capitalist organization.
  - Autonomous Zone (Collective), 1996 (Box 13)
  - AWARE, Inc. (New York, NY), 1953-1959 (Box 13)
  - Ayn Rand Institute, undated (Box 13)
- B, 1886-2012; 6 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 2 oversize shared boxes
  - Babson's Statistical Organization, 1918-1919 (Box 13)
  - Babylon Press, undated (Box 13)
  - Bach Mai Committee, undated (Box 13)
  - Bail Out, undated (Box 13)
  - Bail Out the People Movement, 2008- (Box 13)
  - Baltimore Gay Alliance, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Baltimore Labor College: Brochure, undated (Box 13)
  - Baltimore Urban League, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Banbury Co-operative Industrial Society, undated (Box 13)
  - Band of Mercy, circa 2012 (Box 13)
  - Bar None (Firm), 1975 (Box 13)
    Bar None was a prisoner solidarity group.
  - Barnard Women's Liberation, undated (Box 13)
  - Barricada Collective, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Baruch Afrikan Student Senate (New York), undated (Box 13)
  - Basic Pamphlets (New York, NY), 1957-1975, undated (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Center for Alternative Education (Serial: Prisma), 1974 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Communist Union, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Ecumenical Committee of Concern for Chile, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Institute, 1966-1970 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Paul Robeson Centennial Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Research Collective, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
  - Bay Area Student Committee for the Abolition of the House Committee on Un-American Activities (HUAC), undated (Box 13)
  - Beasely Books: Catalogs 1, 84-100 (Box 13)
  - Beasely Books: Catalogs 101-123 (Box 13)
  - Beaver Conference Farm, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Bedford-Styvesant Restoration Corporation, 1970 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Beehive Design Collective, 2008- (Box 13)
  - Benjamin Rush Society, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
  - Berkeley Art Museum/ Pacific Film Archive, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Berkeley-Oakland Women's Union, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Berkeley Women's Health Collective, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation I, 1966-1985, undated (Box 13)
  - Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation II, 1966-1985, undated (Box 13)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company, circa 1916 (Box 13)
  - Between Classes: A Conference on Academic Labor (New York, NY), 1996 (Box 13)
  - Between the Lines (Ontario, Canada): Catalog, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Bewick Press, 1973- (Box 13)
  - BeyondVoting.org, undated (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 163-190 (Box 14)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 191-205 (Box 14)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 206-220 (Box 14)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 221-235 (Box 14)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 236-249 (Box 14)
  - Bibliomania: Vols. 250-317, non-inclusive (Box 14)
  - Biblioteca Publica Arus (Barcelona, Spain): Brochure, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Bibliotheque de Documentation Internationale Contemporaine (France), 2000-2006 (Box 14)
  - Big Business Day, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Big Flame: Pamphlets, 1977-1988, undated (Box 14)
  - Big Mountain Defense-Offence Committee (Flagstaff, AZ), undated (Box 14)
  - Big Red Media (Brooklyn, NY), undated (Box 14)
  - Bill of Rights Conference (New York), 1949 (Box 14)
  - Billboard Liberation Front, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Billionaires for Bush, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Billy Dean Smith Defense Committee, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Birth Press, undated (Box 14)
  - Black and Green Network, 2003- (Box 14)
  - Black & Red, 1969-1974, undated (Box 14)
  - Black and Third World Women's Alliance, undated (Box 14)
  - Black August Hip Hop Collective, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Bart Brigade, undated (Box 14)
    Black Bart Brigade was a subsidiary of Vocations for Social Change.
  - Black Concern (New York, NY), undated (Box 14)
  - Black Cross Collective, 2001- (Box 14)
  - Black Flag (London, U.K), 1976 (Box 14)
  - Black Flag Anarchists (New York, NY), 1967 (Box 14)
  - Black Graphics International, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
  - Black Hills Alliance of South Dakota, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Black Liberation Army, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Liberation Front, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Liberation Press, 1980, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Lung Association, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Mask (New York, NY), 1966-1967, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Collective, 1996-1997 (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party I, 1966-1974, 2003, undated (Box 14, Box 122, Folder 20, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 13)
  - Black Panther Party II, 1967-1974, 2003, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party III, 1967-1974, 2003, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party IV, 1967-1974, 2003, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party V, 1967-1974, 2003, undated (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party: Campaigns to Free Political Prisoners, circa 2012 (Box 14)
  - Black Panther Party: Committee to Defend the Panther 21 (New York, NY), 1970s (Box 15)
  - Black Panther Party: Committee to Defend the Panthers (New York, NY), 1970s (Box 15)
  - Black Panther Party: Committee to Free the SF 8, 2007- (Box 15)
  - Black Panther Party: New York Panther Defense Committee, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Black Party, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Black People's Socialist League, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Planet Radical Bookstore (Baltimore, MD), 2000- (Box 15)
  - Black Power, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Black Radical Congress, 2000, undated (Box 15)
  - Black River Movement, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Black Rose (Boston, MA), undated (Box 15)
  - Black Rose Books, 1970-2007 (Box 15)
  - Black Solidarity Day (New York, NY), undated (Box 15)
  - Black Star Productions, 1971 (Box 15)
  - Black Swan Press: Pamphlets, 1970-1971, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Vanguard Party, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Veterans for Social Justice, 1985-1992 (Box 15)
  - Black Women's United Front, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Black Workers Conference Committee, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Workers Congress I, 1971-1974, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Workers Congress II, 1971-1974, undated (Box 15)
  - Black Workers Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Blackout Books (New York, NY), 1998 (Box 15)
  - Blast Group (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 15)
  - Block Development Project (New York, NY) I, 1966, undated (Box 15)
  - Block Development Project (New York, NY) II, 1966, undated (Box 15)
  - Bloomington Defense Committee, undated (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Blue Triangle Network, undated (Box 15)
  - Bluestockings Women's Bookstore (New York, NY), undated (Box 15, Box Shared Tamiment 175, Folder 18)
  - Bobby Seale Brigade (George Washington University, Washington, DC), 1970 (Box 15)
  - Body Politic, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Bogalusa Committee for Concern, undated (Box 15)
  - Bolerium Books I, undated (Box 15)
  - Bolerium Books II, undated (Box 15)
  - Bolerium Books III, 1880-2015 (Box 15)
  - Bolshevik Club, undated (Box 15)
  - Bolshevik League of the U.S., 1980, undated (Box 15)
  - Bolshevik Tendency, 1988- (Box 15)
  - Book Forum, undated (Box 15)
  - Booklyn (Brooklyn, NY), 2002 (Box 15)
  - Bookmarks: The Socialist Bookshop (London, U.K), 1977-2002 (Box 15)
  - Books New China, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Books Not Bombs, 2003- (Box 15)
  - Books Through Bars, 2009- (Box 15)
  - Boro Park Action Committee, 1936 (Box 15)
  - Boston Alliance Against Registration and the Draft, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
  - Boston Anti-Authoritarian Movement, 2008 (Box 15)
  - Boston Area Foreign Students Anti-Imperialist Study Group, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Area Socialist Organization, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Boston City-Wide Tenants' Union, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Draft Resistance Group, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Boston Eight, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Federation of Neighborhood Houses, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Fight Black Organization: Heating Oil Campaign, 1979- (Box 15)
  - Boston Trade Union College: Course Catalog, 1925 (Box 15)
  - Boston Unemployed Committee, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Win the Peace Committee, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Boston Women United, 1971, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Women's Abortion Action Coalition, undated (Box 15)
  - Boston Women's Health Book Collective, undated (Box 15)
  - Bound Together (Bookstore): Catalog, 1993 (Box 15)
  - Boycott Japanese Goods Committee of Greater Boston, circa 1940s (Box 15)
  - Boycott the Boathouse, undated (Box 15)
  - Bradley Manning Support Network, undated (Box 15)
  - Brandeis Faculty Group to Oppose the War in Viet-Nam, undated (Box 15)
  - Brandeis May 2nd Committee, undated (Box 15)
  - Brazilian Committee for Amnesty, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Bread and Puppet Theatre, 1967-2012, undated (Box 15)
  - Bread and Roses, 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - Bread for the World, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Bread not Bombs, undated (Box 15)
  - Breakdown Press, 2010- (Box 15)
  - Brecht Forum I, 1999-2010, undated (Box 15)
  - Brecht Forum II, 1985-2010, undated (Box 16)
  - Bridges Robertson Schmidt Defense Committee, 1949-1952 (Box 16)
  - Bring the Ruckus, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Bring the Troops Home Now, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Bristol Gap, 2001 (Box 16)
  - British Anti-War Movement: Youth Congress, undated (Box 16)
  - British Association for Labour Legislation: Pamphlet, undated (Box 16)
  - British Canadian Co-operative Society, 1949, undated (Box 16)
  - British Columbia Blackout/B.C. Blackout, 1982 (Box 16)
  - British Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners in Russia, circa 1924 (Box 16)
  - British League of Esperantist Socialists, 1923 (Box 16)
  - British-Polish Friendship Society, undated (Box 16)
  - British Socialist Party, 1919-1920 (Box 16)
  - British-Soviet Friendship Society, 1955 (Box 16)
  - British Vietnam Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 16)
  - Broadside Press (Detroit, MI), 1970-1973 (Box 16)
  - Broadway Local, 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Bronx Action for Justice and Peace, undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Coalition, undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Committee to Win the Peace, undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Conference for Racial and Religious Unity, 1944 (Box 16)
  - Bronx Consumer Cooperative Society, Inc., undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Council on Rents and Housing, undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Free Fellowship, 1930, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Bronx Frontier Development Corporation, undated (Box 16)
  - Bronx Workers Club, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Beachniks for Peace, 1967 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Bureau of Charities, 1912 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Civil Rights Congress, 1952 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Coalition Against NAFTA, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Coaltion for Peace and Justice, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Committee of One Thousand, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Food Conference, 2009 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn For Peace, 2007-2009, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Freedom Democratic Movement, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Hand Laundrymen's Association: 20th Anniversary Souvenir Journal, 1947 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Heights Peace Action, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Heights Peace Coalition, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Labor Lyceum Association, 1907 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Moratorium Committee, 1971 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Parents for Peace, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Residents for Peace, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Resistance, 1968 (Box 16)
    Brooklyn Resistance was an Anti-Vietnam War organization.
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Wallace for President Committee, undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklyn Women's Commission (Brooklyn Communist Women's Conference), undated (Box 16)
  - Brooklynites Against Apartheid, undated (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY), 1925-1926. 1936 (Box 16, Box 122, Folder 22)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY) I, 1927-1929 (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY) II, 1927-1929 (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY), 1929-1931 (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY), 1932-1934 (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY), 1935-1939 (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY) I, undated (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Katonah, NY) II, undated (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College Players (Katonah, NY), 1926, undated (Box 16)
  - Brookwood Labor College Players (Katonah, NY), 1937 (Box 16)
  - Brotherhood Party, 1961 (Box 16)
  - Brown & Sharpe Mutual Relief Association, 1886 (Box 16)
  - Brown Radical Education Project, undated (Box 16)
  - Brownsville Labor Lyceum Association, 1923, 1936 (Box 16)
  - Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry I, 1921-1938 (Box 16)
  - Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry II, 1921-1938 (Box 16)
  - Buddhist Socialist Bloc in Vietnam, circa 1964 (Box 17)
  - Buddy Cochran Defense Committee (East Point, GA), undated (Box 17)
  - Buffalo Creek Massacre Coalition, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Building Trades Employer's Association, 1903-1981 (Box 17)
  - Bulgarian Communist Party, circa 1940s, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Bull Moose Movement, 2010- (Box 17)
  - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1965 (Box 17)
  - Bunker Hill Committee, undated (Box 17)
  - Bureau D'Editions, 1919-1938 (Box 17)
  - Bureau International Socialiste, 1948 (Box 17)
  - Bureau of Cooperative Medicine, 1937-1940 (Box 17)
  - Bureau of Municipal Research (Philadelphia, PA), 1920 (Box 17)
  - Bureau Socialiste International, 1907-1908 (Box 17)
  - Burning Issues, undated (Box 17)
  - Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace, 1969, undated (Box 17)
  - Butcher, the Baker, the Candlestick Maker: Images of Labor, 1978 (Box 17)
  - By Any Means Necessary (BAMN), 2003 (Box 17)
    By Any Means Necessary was an organization focused on affirmative action.
  - Byelorussian-American Association, 1918-2005 (Box 17)
- C, 1899-2016; 16.25 Linear Feet in 15 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Cabral-Tubman Center for Marxist-Leninist Education: Course Schedule, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Cadorit Conference, 1955 (Box 17)
  - Cahiers du communisme, 1958 (Box 17)
  - California Emergency Defense Committee, undated (Box 17)
  - California Homemakers Association, undated (Box 17)
  - California Joint Immigration Committee, 1934-1936, undated (Box 17)
  - California Labor School, 1943-1952, undated (Box 17)
  - California Newsreel, 1980-1998 (Box 17)
  - California Union Against Militarism, 1916 (Box 17)
  - California Working Group, 1993 (Box 17)
  - Californian Labor League for Political Education, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Call Association (Cooperative Commonwealth), 1951-1958 (Box 17)
  - Call Bookstore (New York, NY), undated (Box 17)
  - Call Radio Bureau, 1941-1942 (Box 17)
  - Calumet Community Congress (Indiana), 1970 (Box 17)
  - Cambridge Committee to End the War in Vietnam, undated (Box 17)
  - Cambridge Neighborhood Committee on Vietnam, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Cambridge Tenants' Organizing Committee, undated (Box 17)
  - Cambridge Vietnam Committee, undated (Box 17)
  - Camp Kinderland (Hopewell Junction, NY), 1960-1984, undated (Box 17, Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Camp McCoy 3 Defense Committee (Madison, WI; New York, NY; East Cleveland, OH), 1971- (Box 17)
  - Camp Midvale (Midvale, NJ), 1940-1997, undated (Box 17)
  - Camp Tamiment: Brochures), undated (Box 17)
  - Camp Three Arrows, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Camp Wa-Chi-Chi (NJ), 1947-1949 (Box 17)
  - Campaign for a Democratic Foreign Policy, 1976, undated (Box 17)
  - Campaign for a National Health Program Now, undated (Box 17)
  - Campaign for a People's Fightback, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Campaign for Economic Justice at NYU, 1997-2007 (Box 17, Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Campaign for Labor Rights: Brochure, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Campaign for Peace and Democracy, 1982-1990 (Box 17)
  - Campaign for Political Rights (U.S.), 1982 (Box 17)
  - Campaign for Youth's Needs, 1930s (Box 17)
  - Campaign to End the Death Penalty, undated (Box 17)
  - Campaign to Oppose the Return of the Khmer Rouge, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
  - Campaign to Protect Airline Safety and Jobs, undated (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Campaign to Stop Government Spying, 1977 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Campaign to Stop Killer Coke, circa 2009, undated (Box 17)
    Campaign to Stop Killer Coke was an anti-corporate activist organization.
  - Campus Anti-War Network, 2005, undated (Box 17)
  - Campus Draft Opposition, undated (Box 17)
  - Campus Party (City College of New York), undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian-American Rally to Stop the War in Vietnam, undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Canadian Committee on Labour History: Catalogs, 1998-1999 (Box 17)
  - Canadian Communist League (Marxist-Leninist), 1976, undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian Federation of Students, 1999 (Box 17)
    The materials in this file represent the Canadian Federation of Students protest of the World Trade Organization.
  - Canadian Labour Defense League, 1931, undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian Labor Party: Ontario Section, 1924 (Box 17)
  - Canadian League Against War and Fascism, undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian Party of Labor: Steel Strike, Hamilton, 1946 (Box 17)
  - Canadian Peace Conference, 1960-1971 (Box 17)
  - Canadian Peace Conference: Jewish Committee, undated (Box 17)
  - Canadian Peace Congress, 1952, 1965 (Box 18)
  - Canadian Women's Educational Press (Toronto, Canada), undated (Box 18)
  - Capital District Coalition to Sign the Agreement Now, undated (Box 18)
  - Capitalism Nature Socialism, circa 2011 (Box 18)
  - Capitol District Sign the Agreement Now Coalition, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Caplan-Schmidt Defense Committee, 1915 (Box 18)
  - Caravan Theatre, undated (Box 18)
  - Caribbean Correspondence: Publications, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Caribbean Labour Congress, undated (Box 18)
  - Carnegie Endowment, undated (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace Library, 1940 (Box 18)
  - Carnival Against Capitalism, 2002 (Box 18)
  - Casa Chile Salvador Allende (New York, NY), undated (Box 18)
  - Casa de las Americas (New York, NY), 1972 (Box 18)
  - Casa Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Cascadia Summer, 2003 (Box 18)
  - Catholic Campus Ministry of Rider College, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Catholic Committee for Democratic Socialism, circa 1960s (Box 18)
  - Catholic Cooperative Committee, 1944 (Box 18)
  - Catholic Information Society, 1947, undated (Box 18)
  - Catholic Peace Fellowship, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Catholic Worker, 1936-1974 (Box 18, Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Catholics for Free Choice, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Center for Campus Organizing (Cambridge, MA), 1995-1996 (Box 18)
  - Center for Change Collective (CFC), 1974 (Box 18)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1973-1988 (Box 122, Folder 30, Box 18)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights (New York NY) I, 1971-2002, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights (New York NY) II, 1980-2007, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Creative Democracy, 2002 (Box 18)
  - Center for Cuban Studies I, 1973-1979, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Cuban Studies II, 1973-1979, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Defense Information (Washington, DC), 1985, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Educational Reform, 1970, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Labor Research and Studies: "Union Members' Voting Patterns in the 1984 Presidential Election: Evidence from a Rustbelt and a Sunbelt State" Florida International University, July 1988 (Box 18)
  - Center for Libertarian Studies, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for International Studies (Cornell University), undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Marxist Education (New York, NY), 1970-1976, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for National Security Studies (Washington, DC), 1978 (Box 18)
  - Center for Policy Research, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Center for Popular Economics, 1983-1990 (Box 18)
  - Center for Radical Research, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for a Stateless Society, 2011, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Social Action, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Socialist History, 2010- (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Popular Culture, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions I, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions II, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions III, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions IV, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions V, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions VI, 1959-1966, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for United Labor Action, 1971-1979, undated (Box 18)
  - Center for Women's Studies and Services, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Center of Concern, 1979- (Box 18)
  - Center to Protect Workers' Rights, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Central America Health Rights Network, 1986 (Box 121)
  - Central Brooklyn Mobilization for Political Action, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors I, 1954-1986, undated (Box 19)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors II, 1954-1986, undated (Box 19)
  - Central Committee of Correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 19)
  - Central Co-operative Wholesale (U.S.), 1933 (Box 19)
  - Central High School of Needle Trades, 1938 (Box 19)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1967-1974 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Central Labor Bodies Conference, 1920 (Box 19)
  - Central Museum of Labor (Tyovaen Keskusmueo) (Finland), 1990- (Box 19)
  - Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists I, 1974-1979 (Box 19)
  - Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists II, 1974-1979 (Box 19)
  - Central States Co-operative League, 1936-1939, undated (Box 19)
  - Centre D'Etudes Socialistes (Paris, France), 1969 (Box 19)
  - Centre for Socialist Education (Nottingham, England), 1968 (Box 19)
  - Centre International de Recherches sur L'Anarchisme, 1996-2002 (Box 19)
  - Centre International de Recherches sur L'Anarchisme (Marseille, France), 2002-2003 (Box 19)
  - Centro Cultural Pablo de la Torriente Brau, 2001-2002 (Box 19)
  - Centro Estudiantil de la Universidad de Trabajadores, 1978 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Centro de Estudios Puertorriquenos (CUNY, Hunter College, New York, NY), 1984 (Box 19)
  - Centro de la Raza (Seattle, WA), 1980 (Box 19)
  - Centro de Orientacion y Accion Social, undated (Box 19)
  - Centro Studi Libertari G. Pinelli, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Challenge, 1950 (Box 19)
  - Challenging the Color Line: Confronting the Issues of Race and Class in the Era of Global Capitalism (New York, NY), 2002 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America I, 1934-1970 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America II, 1934-1970 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America III, 1934-1970 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America IV, 1934-1970 (Box 19)
  - Chaney Goodman Schwerner Memorial Collection, 1964 (Box 19)
  - Channel L Working Groups, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Chashama Theatre, undated (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Chardon Press: Catalog, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Charleroi Progressive Co-operative Association (Pennsylvania), 1905-1912 (Box 19)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company I, 1899- (Box 19)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company II, 1899- (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company III, 1899- (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company IV, 1899- (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company V, 1899- (Box 20)
  - Charles Street for Peace, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Charlottesville Resistance, 1975 (Box 20)